So guys today is Tuesday and
chicken is for ₹800 and egg is for ₹470.  The remaining cost of oil and
spices will be Rs 22,300.  Will
I be able to earn ₹1000 in this amount or not?   Let's see.
So I gave one roll to this brother
and one roll to this brother and
Alhamdulillah I sold 60 rolls and a
child came to the shop.  I told him I wanted paratha.
So I quickly gave a chicken roll to the child.  This
little kid is a fan of my role.  After that
these betting brothers come to the shop.
Dealt with all of these one by one.  Very
few betting brothers came today.  Then these
children went in front of the shop and we quickly came back.  After
eating food at home, I went back to the shop.  So we get
four customers.  After finishing all this,
Alhamdulillah, I had good sales till 3:30 pm
but today the sales were
very slow.  I was sitting idle so I
quickly cleaned the shop and
filled the dustbin with garbage and then sat comfortably and
drank water.  Then these kids came and told us five
chicken rolls.  So I quickly packed five chicken rolls and gave them to him.
After that, these little
children were eating chicken rolls comfortably and happily.   All the
customers sitting there wanted
chicken roll.  This brother came and told me five
egg rolls.  So after quickly giving chicken rolls to all of us, he
quickly packed five egg rolls for brother
and finished all the chicken rolls.
I still have 240 eggs left.
Let me go home and tell you about today's sales.
Today my sales were ₹3130, from which please
tell me in the comments how much profit you guys made.